You spoiled brat ! You brat , where are you ?
You think you can escape from me ?
It 's ok , my child . Don 't cry .
Look at your brothers and sisters , they are such good kids .
Pom , are you sure Chaba was the one who abducted the kids ?
You 're sure about that ? She looks so frail .
She can barely walk .
I heard Pang 's voice coming from in here .
Be still my child . So you won 't be afraid to look at me anymore .
Don 't worry , it won 't hurt .
I 'll be quick .
Get out !
- Jesus ! It 's me , Mom . - Mom , help me please !
You bitch , don 't you dare touch my kid .
No !
Stop !
My child ...
Stop ! Don 't touch my kids .
Crazy bitch , your kids were burnt to death .
How could you do this to my kids ?
Kill her !
Kill her ! Kill her right now ! Kill her !
Hey Toh , why are you sitting here ?
You don 't want to go back in to see your work ?
Last night I already watched it once .
So how was it ? You weren 't happy ?
Um ... I think ...
I 'm going to edit the scene where Chaba was hung .
Hello , what 's up ?
Pang ...
- Pang ... what 's wrong ? Pang are you alright ? - Leave me alone !
She is here .
Chaba is here .
Pang , don 't be afraid .
Pang , you are having a bad dream .
Who 's that ?
Toh is that you ?
Toh ?
Shit ! Shane , the reel is running out .
Hey , this is the ghost movie showing in theatres next week .
Where did you get these reels ?
The production team had a private screening .
Is it scary ? I really want to see this movie .
No , I don 't even like scary movies so I won 't see it .
Gosh , you think you 're just too cool , huh ?
So you 're so chicken , you don 't even dare to watch it ?
It 's not like that . I just don 't like to watch stupid movies .
Is it ready yet ?
No , not yet . I just got around to it .
So just swap these reels in for now . They 're outside , waiting for the film .
Yod ,
are you sure we won 't get in trouble for this ?
You pussy . It 's too late to back out now .
If you want your money now , just say so .
This is your share . Here 's half now .
As for the rest , I 'll get it to you later .
Hello , is this Joe ? Tonight , I want to bet on three matches .
On Calcio .
OK , yes Cagiari , Milan , and Palermo .
Palermo ! You idiot , not Palamo Picasso .
Yeah , 1,000 baht .
Yes , 1,000 on all 3 matches .
So are you leaving now ?
Hello ?
Thank you .
I didn 't think you would remember my birthday .
Som ,
happy birthday .
Hey , am I interrupting something ?
Yod !
What the hell is wrong with you , Shane ?
Shane !
Yod !
- Yod , are you ok ? - That freaking hurts man !
Oh my gosh !
I 'm sorry .
Som , did you really have to hit me ?
I didn 't know it was you .
Everyone already ate everything .
I wanted to taste your cake .
I really didn 't think you were going to remember my birthday .
I don 't remember , but your boyfriend did .
Cheers ! Cheers man ! Pepsi ? Whatever !
Bro , try not to drink too much . Tomorrow you have to go to work .
Som , you 're my sister , not my mother .
It 's just a little , I will be fine .
I got to go now .
Why , what 's the hurry ?
I won 't be able to wake up .
Ok , it 's up to you .
You know , a petite girl like you
going home alone late like this is not safe .
I told you to move in with me .
Bro , your place is way too dirty for anyone to live .
Even the rats have to leave .
You 're so dramatic .
I 'm going now , bye .
Go ...
Isn 't the weather nice tonight ?
- Um , Som about the watch I took ... - Forget about it .
Hey Shane , you have the worst luck man .
I really think Som hates your guts .
Uh ... Yod ?
Yod , are you sure security is not going to walk in ?
Shit man , you know I got your back .
Don 't you need the money to get Som 's watch ?
Just hurry and get it done .
" Taweesup Pawnshop "
" Pawing : 1 Lady watch "
Shane ! What are you doing ?
Why are you taking my watch ?
I just need to borrow it , Som .
You 're gonna trade it for drugs , right ?
- C 'mon Som I will give it back later . - No ! You can 't have it ! Give it to me !
Let go !
Som ...
Oh shit !
Damn it !
Who is that ?
What are you doing here ?
Uh , I am looking for my stuff .
Yesterday , while I was watching a movie , I must 've dropped it .
Ok , have you seen Yod ?
Um , no . I just got here .
Where the heck is he ?
Why , do you have something urgent for him ? If I run into Yod , I will let him know .
Yesterday Yod returned the wrong print .
Now everyone is scrambling to find it .
They are worried the film will be pirated .
Som where are you ?
Please go get the posters at the entrance for me .
Yes , I am on the way .
Dude , why is the door locked , are you wacking off in there ?
Oh , I accidentally locked it .
Dude , do you know the result of last night 's games ?
You won all your bets !
- Today your shift ends in the afternoon right ? - Yes .
Can you do me a favor ?
Go collect my winnings for me .
Then take my share of the winnings and this money and go redeem my stuff for me .
- I got to go now . - Ok .
Don 't forget .
Yod ...
Yod .
Shit ! Damn it !
Hey Shane .
Where is your supervisor ?
When I call , no one picks up .
I really don 't know .
So the both of you think you can screw me over , huh ?
So , where 's that movie
that I asked you to copy ?
Right now all the theatre staff is on the lookout .
About the money , I 'll find a way to pay you back .
I don 't want your money . You got to find a way to copy that film .
I want to deliver the copy before its release date .
Hey Pom , are you sure it 's Chaba who abducted the kids ?
Seriously , I 've heard Pang 's voice from the inside .
Pang ! Pang !
" Calling ... Yod "
Phong !
What is it , Pom ?
Hurry , take the girl with you and run !
Chaba 's ghost is back to take revenge .
Everyone else is dead .
Hurry ! Grab your sister . Go Phong ! Get out of here .
Yod ?
Who is that ?
" Calling ... Som "
- Yesterday were you at work ? - Yes .
When you were on your way out , did you see Yod ?
No , I didn 't see him .
Did you see the film ?
- Which film are you talking about ? - The Film
No , I didn 't see it .
And do you know where the print could be sent to ?
Shane ,
are you free ?
Please come and help us assemble this Standee .
Som , ever since the both of you broke up ,
you haven 't given any thought of ever talking to him ?
If I have nothing to talk about why should I talk to him ?
You knew that Shane was high on drugs .
He didn 't mean to hurt you .
Who knows ... One day , he might not be there , and you 're going to regret it .
" Base on the most horrifying true story . "
Why are you doing this ?
You want to go to jail ?
Don 't tell me that you need the money for drugs .
Is Yod part of this too ? Where is he ?
Yod ...
Yod is dead , Som .
Shane , what are you talking about ?
This might sound ridiculous ,
but there is something more to this movie .
The ghost in the movie , I think she is for real .
Shane , are you high ?
No , Som .
Som , take a look at this .
Last night , I was screening the movie again .
I ...
I noticed Yod 's corpse in the movie .
In the movie ?
Ever since I watched this movie ,
I 've seen her haunting me .
Don 't watch the movie , Som or else you will end up like me !
Why ? If I want to watch , what are you going to do ? Hit me ?
" Calling ... Yod "
Sorry , the number you 've dialed ...
Shane , why the hell are you sitting here for ?
I thought you went home already .
Here is the stuff you asked me to get for you .
Luckily , I redeemed it in time . Or else it might have been sold .
Open the door !
Let me out ! Help !
Open it !
Shane !
Shane , what 's wrong ?
Please help him .
Shane , what happened ?
What the hell is going on ?
I have no clue what 's scaring the shit out of him !
But this time he is really in bad shape .
What else could be causing this ...
except for him getting high and overdosing again ?
Som , you know what ? Ever since you broke up . He stopped using drugs .
- See you tomorrow . - Ok .
" Production crew of felt the curse . "
" Electricity went out during the shoot , staff prayed for forgiveness . "
" Chaba "
" Chaba / Wikipedia "
" Hanging "
" Eye-gouging "
" An insane woman captures the children and gouged their eyes out . "
" Do you still remember this house ? ! ? "
" Here , an insane woman captured children and "
" gouged their eyes , believing they were her own . "
" Do you still remember this house ? ! ? "
" 30 years ago , Mrs Chaba Ngamsri , "
" an insane lady who captured "
" kids and gouged their eyes out , thought they were her own . "
" The villagers found out , "
" broke in and swarmed Chaba , and hung her . "
Thank you for taking care of me , Som .
Shane ,
you know that story you told me
about Yod
and the ghost in the movie ?
I just don 't know , it 's so hard for me to believe .
But ...
I came across the story you told me from the internet and
it 's exactly as you told me .
Shane , if everything that is happening to you takes place exactly like the movie ,
then how does the movie end ?
In the end ,
the hero dies .
He breaks into an abandoned house to find Chaba 's body to cremate .
But he doesn 't make it .
What if ?
We can make it ?
Chaba 's body might still be in this house .
" Until now , Chaba 's body still has not been found . "
Shane ,
look !
This can 't be ?
There should be another room here ?
Shane , everything might not be exactly like the movie .
Som .
Shane ...
Shane , are you ok ?
Shane , can you hear me ?
Shane ...
Shane , I will be right back .
Shane , are you ok ? Are you hurt anywhere ?
I 'm fine .
Let 's get out of here .
Shane ...
Shane climb up here quickly .
Shane , what 's wrong ?
Shane , what 's wrong ? Shane , come with me .
Just come with me .
Shane , I told you to come this way .
Shane ...
Shane , hurry this way .
Come with me .
Go away !
Shane ...
Shane ,
it 's me Som .
Shane , it 's ok now .
It 's me Som .
I am going to die like Yod .
I got your watch back to return to you ...
but I accidentally broke it again .
I don 't think I will be around to get it fixed this time .
Shane , don 't talk like that .
You are going to be alright .
Mr. Rashane , please go to the examination room .
From what I can see , you have a fracture in your left arm .
I will give you some medicine for pain . Take some and you can go home .
So , what were the two of you doing in that house ?
We were looking for more information
to do a news story about Chaba 's death .
What are you talking about ? Chaba is not dead .
Doctor , what do you mean ?
Right after Chaba was taken by the villagers to be hanged ,
the police arrived just in time to send her to the hospital and saved her life .
However , all the villagers believed she died . So the story was forgotten .
There ... there she is - Chaba .
Are you sure that old lady is really Chaba ?
Yes , I 'm sure .
So if Chaba is not dead
then who was that woman you saw ?
Who is she ?
Is it possible that everything is just your imagination ?
Shane ...
Shane ?
Som ,
the person that I keep seeing is her .
Shane , you mean this actress ?
" , starring Ingchan "
Thank you .
Are you looking for somebody ?
Nobody has come to work at this company for over a week .
" Cast and Crew "
" Crew List : "
" Behind the scene : villagers search for missing kids . "
" Behind the scene : Chaba was hung . "
Sorry , the number you 've dialed ...
Ok , ready ?
Action !
Kill her ! Kill her !
Cut .
Action .
Yeah ! Kill her ! Kill her !
- Action ! - Help ! Somebody help !
- Cut ! - Take 25
Action !
Help ! Help me !
Cut ! Damn it ! Get you act together !
Jeab ,
you call this acting ?
Hey , your foot position is wrong . You know what I mean ?
What are you afraid of ? Your tensing all the wrong body parts .
You look like you 're dancing , not dying .
Try to focus this time !
Action !
Cut ! You don 't even have any lines .
All you have to do is act like you 're dying . You can 't even do that !
Action !
Kill her ! Kill her !
Cut !
Damn , why is it so difficult ?
Can we try it again , one more time ?
If she can 't get it this time , then Jeab , you go change and take her place instead .
What are you scared of ? I don 't get it !
What 's not safe about this ? See ? It 's safe . Ok ?
How many times are you going to repeat the same mistake ?
Everybody is waiting on you .
Can we film already , damn it !
Ok , ready everyone ? Just one more time ok ?
Get out of my way !
Help ! Help !
Hey , Jeab . Jeab . Come here .
- What ? - Look at this , the sling is broken .
Oh damn ! Stop ! Everybody stop !
The sling broke . Toh , the sling is broken .
Hey , get her down from there . Get her down . Cut ! Cut !
Get her down . Come on help her down .
Get her down .
I 'm sorry ...
Shane .
Where are you going ?
Som ,
if I don 't make it back tomorrow ,
don 't go to the theatre .
Don 't watch the movie .
Why ?
The scene where Chaba died in the movie is for real .
Ingchan ... she really died .
Whoever watches that scene
will die too .
And what are you going to do , Shane ?
Shane , where are you going ?
Shane .
Som , I am sorry .
Shane ...
Shane .
Hey Shane , keeping to yourself lately ?
Where are you going in such a hurry ?
I 've been waiting for you for many days now .
Don 't tell me that you 're going to try to skip out on me again .
The exit is to your right .
Yeah , the movie just ended . I 'm leaving now .
Hey wait up ! What 's the hurry ?
Hey Shane , keeping to yourself lately ?
Where are you going in such a hurry ?
I 've been waiting for you for many days .
Don 't tell me that you 're going to try to skip out on me again .
The exit is to your right .
Yeah , the movie just ended . I 'm leaving now .
Hey wait up ! What 's the hurry ?
Hey ! Shane , keeping to yourself lately ?
Where are you going in such a hurry ?
I 've been waiting for you for many days now .
Don 't tell me that you 're going to try to skip out on me again .
Piece of shit !
Som .
Shane .
Som !
You really want to see me die ?
You really want to see ? ! Here look !
Look at me !
You really want to see me die ?
You really want to see ? !
Shane ?
Yod !
Shane !
at 14 : 15
is now ready for showing .
" A Film by Sophon Sakdaphisit "
You really want to see me die ?
Subtitles by LeapinLar